{
    "id": "0d810f9710614c499d9407ce3cdf9869",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Don’t make a such a bother ………………….. which dress to wear.",
            "description": "When bother is a noun, it can be used with over or about.",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "about",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "57ac7296afed4c0281fedf919c1c880c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The ship sank ……………………. the bottom.",
            "description": "In and at shows position. To indicates ideas such as movement and direction.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "44b52c9d6a5c4570a855ea9597d3e1f4"
        },
        {
            "question": "She spanked the boy ………………………. his bottom.",
            "description": "On indicates position on the surface. ",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fcc29225b66a447281ee5eeed79981c9"
        },
        {
            "question": "In olden days the poor had to depend ……………………. the parish’s bounty.",
            "description": "Depend is used with on. ",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "on",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "06a67d66099240728c665f694b9f97b8"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was punished ………………………. a boyish prank.",
            "description": "For shows the purpose or the reason. ",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5c86b0512dc14aa892be1a80243782ac"
        },
        {
            "question": "The typist botched the work and had to start ……………………..",
            "description": "To start over is to do it again. ",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "over",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "25aa296bd9824b0c8e152ed5a6acfe9d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The guest speaker turned ………………………….. to be a deadly bore.",
            "description": "Turn out means prove to be the case. ",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1418a87975034db89508f79cd667d1b3"
        },
        {
            "question": "The policemen showed great bravery …………………………. the face of danger.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a2ddea95e97b48e2bee93894ce05fd8b"
        },
        {
            "question": "We were stunned …………………………. the breadth of the mountain range.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "with",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7dfd2f6d5d704bcdb09e6251575676cf"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mosquitoes breed ……………………….. stagnant water.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "into"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9100f267a298473cad99a50f1f14a68d"
        },
        {
            "question": "A storm is brewing ……………………….. the horizon.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "over",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2babe228768946e8803881b0edb98ca2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her bridal gown was ……………………….. pure silk.",
            "description": "Of shows the material with which something is made. ",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "up",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e98b95a024e84cbba69eef0780914f33"
        }
    ]
}